barcelona-tourist-guide.com 2010-12-22

# Privacy Policy

Your privacy is important to us. We do not disclose any personal details that you have given us unless you specifically ask us to.

In providing reviews, comments or feedback to our site you have read and agreed to our terms of use of your comments which you can read by clicking on the following link Terms To Providing Feedback

When you sign up to our free newsletter we keep your details strictly private and never rent, sell, or in anyway disclose your e-mail address to any other company.

www.barcelona-tourist-guide.com strives to maintain the highest standards of decency, fairness and integrity in all our operations. Likewise, we are dedicated to protecting our customers', consumers' and online visitors' privacy on our website.

## Personal Information

**www.barcelona-tourist-guide.com** collects personally identifiable information from the visitors to our website only on a voluntary basis. Personal information collected on a voluntary basis may include name, postal address, email address, company name and telephone number etc.

This information is collected if you request information from us, participate in a contest or sweepstakes, and sign up to join our email list or request some other service or information from us. The information collected is internally reviewed, used to improve the content of our website, notify our visitors of updates, and respond to visitor enquiries.

Once information is reviewed, it is discarded or stored in our files. Personal information received from any visitor will be used only for internal purposes and will not be sold or provided to third parties unless you specifically ask us to.

## Use of Cookies and Web Beacons

We may use cookies to help you personalize your online experience. Cookies are identifiers that are transferred to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize the sites pages, or register with any of our site's services, a cookie enables www.barcelona-tourist-guide.com to recall your specific information on subsequent visits.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies by modifying your Web browser; however, if you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the site.

A web beacon is a transparent image file used to monitor your journey around a single website or collection of sites. They may be used in association with cookies to understand how visitors interact with the pages and content on the pages of a web site.

We may serve third party advertisements that use cookies and web beacons in the course of ads being served on our web site to ascertain how many times you've seen an advertisement. No personally identifiable information you give us is provided to them for cookie or web beacon use, so they cannot personally identify you with that information on our web site.

Browsers can be set to accept or reject cookies or notify you when a cookie is being sent. Privacy software can be used to override web beacons. Taking  
either of these actions shouldn't cause a problem with our site, should you so choose.

## Children's Online Privacy Protection Act

This website is directed to adults; it is not directed to children under the age of 13. We operate our site in compliance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act, and will not knowingly collect or use personal information from anyone under 13 years of age.

## Non-Personal Information

In some cases, we may collect information about you that is not personally identifiable. We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users' movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. The information collected is used solely for internal review and not shared with other organizations for commercial purposes.

## Release of Information

If **www.barcelona-tourist-guide.com** is sold, the information we have obtained from you through your voluntary participation in our site may transfer to the new owner as a part of the sale in order that the service being provided to you may continue. In that event, you will receive notice through our website of that change in control and practices, and we will make reasonable efforts to ensure that the purchaser honors any opt-out requests you might make of us.

## How You Can Correct or Remove Information

We provide this privacy policy as a statement to you of our commitment to protect your personal information. If you have submitted personal information  
through our website and would like that information deleted from our records or would like to update or correct that information, please click on the Contact Us page and let us know.

## Exclusive rights to use site visitor submitted material reviews/comments/questions/images etc

In sending barcelona-tourist-guide.com a review, comments, questions, images etc (from here on referred to as **submitted material** ) you agree that we may use your submitted material freely as we see fit both on this site and any associated sites that we choose. This will also include any promotions that we deem as fitting or creation of derivative works and translations etc.

When you send your submitted material to **www.barcelona-tourist-guide.com** you agree that we will retain the **exclusive distribution rights** for the submitted material. You also agree that when you send us your submitted material it will not be used on any other websites or publications without our written permission. In sending us your submitted material you confirm that it has not been previously published by any other website or publication. You agree that the submitted material you send to us was originally created by you and that you are the copyright owner of the work.

If you cannot agree to all of the above points please do not send us your submitted material.

## Updates and Effective Date

**www.barcelona-tourist-guide.com** reserves the right to make changes in this policy. If there is a material change in our privacy practices, we will indicate on our site that our privacy practices have changed and provide a link to the new privacy policy. We encourage you to periodically review this policy so that you will know what information we collect and how we use it.

## Website Statistics

This website uses Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. (Google).  Google Analytics uses cookies, which are text files placed on your computer, to help the website analyze how users use the site. The information generated by the cookie about your use of the website (including your IP address) will be transmitted to and stored by Google on servers in the United States . Google will use this information for the purpose of evaluating your use of the website, compiling reports on website activity for website operators and providing other services relating to website activity and internet usage.  Google may also transfer this information to third parties where required to do so by law, or where such third parties process the information on Google's behalf. Google will not associate your IP address with any other data held by Google.  You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser, however please note that if you do this you may not be able to use the full functionality of this website.  By using this website, you consent to the processing of data about you by Google in the manner and for the purposes set out above.

## Internet Advertising

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and would like to know your options in relation to·not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/).  

## Agreeing to These Terms

If you do not agree to **www.barcelona-tourist-guide.com** Privacy Policy as posted here on this website, please do not use this website or any services offered by this web site.

Your use of this web site indicates acceptance of this privacy policy and to our terms and conditions of use of our website which you can find by clicking here.  

* * *

## Related Pages 

[Barcelona Discount Card](http://www.barcelona-tourist-guide.com/en/general/barcelona-card.html) \- Free transport and discounts to many attractions  
[Part II of our Basic Facts includes summary of Spanish Political system](http://www.barcelona-tourist-guide.com/en/general/spain-political-system.html)  

**Tourist personal safety advice when visiting the city.**  
[Car Crime In Barcelona](http://www.barcelona-tourist-guide.com/en/general/barcelona-car-crime-safety-tips.html) \- What you need to know if you intend driving a car in Barcelona to ensure your personal safety  

**Themed vists to Barcelona**  
[Stag Do's in Barcelona](http://www.barcelona-tourist-guide.com/en/general/stag-weekend-barcelona.html) \- How to plan and organize your stag weekend  

* * *

Back To The Top Of The Page
